A Guide to the Black Organizations Council Records, 1982-2017
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Operational Records, 1984-2016
  - Black Cultural Center and Multicultural Center, 1999-2001
    - Mounted Photographs from Black Cultural Center and Multicultural Center Displays (Box 2, Folder 8, Folder 9, Folder 10)
    - Photographs of Displays in the Black Cultural Center and Multicultural Center (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Photographs of Black Cultural Center Art, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Photographs of the Black Cultural Center, Fall 1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of the Black Cultural Center, c.1999-c.2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of the Multicultural Center, c.1999-c.2001 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Photographs of Faculty and Staff, Spring 2000 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Meet Your Community Board, Fall 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People, c.1999-c.2001 (Box 8, Folder 14)